[
    { "question": "", "answer": "" },
    {
        "question": "Countries need to work hard to improve _____ in their poorest areas. Everyone has a right to live in a clean place.",
        "answer": "sanitation"
    },
    {
        "question": "Your drink would be healthier for you if you _____ the amount of sugar you add to it.",
        "answer": "reduce"
    },
    {
        "question": "If you could _____ some time to help us with our final project, we would really appreciate it.",
        "answer": "donate"
    },
    {
        "question": "If you don’t take better care of yourself, you will _____ your health.",
        "answer": "worsen"
    },
    {
        "question": "She wants me to be perfect in every way, but it’s impossible to live up to that _____.",
        "answer": "ideal"
    },
    {
        "question": "Getting a high score on the university entrance exam was quite a _____ for her, but she did well.",
        "answer": "difficulty"
    },
    {
        "question": "The politician had some problems after she accepted a large _____ from a well-known criminal.",
        "answer": "contribution"
    },
    {
        "question": "I’m sorry teacher, but I don’t quite know what this word means. Could you _____ it for me?",
        "answer": "define"
    },
    {
        "question": "I haven’t been sleeping well, and this seems to caused an _____ of pimples on my face.",
        "answer": "outbreak"
    },
    {
        "question": "This country’s _____ has been improving as a result of global trade.",
        "answer": "economy"
    },
    {
        "question": "Congratulations! Getting a perfect score on your driver’s test is quite an _____.",
        "answer": "achievement"
    },
    {
        "question": "I don’t want to _____ the already bad situation with my girlfriend by telling her that I accidentally kissed her twin sister!",
        "answer": "worsen"
    },
    {
        "question": "Heartbreak is a _____ that most of us will experience at one time or another; it’s part of being human.",
        "answer": "difficulty"
    },
    {
        "question": "You can really help the people of the village if you donate some money to that _____.",
        "answer": "charity"
    },
    {
        "question": "I’m sorry to say that there has been another _____ of Covid 19 this month.",
        "answer": "outbreak"
    },
    {
        "question": "I think working overseas would be a wonderful _____ for you.",
        "answer": "experience"
    },
    {
        "question": "After the global _____ finished, many countries changed the way that they created medicines.",
        "answer": "pandemic"
    },
    {
        "question": "If you do a little research on the price of a new car, you can make an _____ decision on how much you should pay.",
        "answer": "informed"
    },
    {
        "question": "I want to volunteer to help a local _____ this summer. I hope I can do some good for the people of my community.",
        "answer": "charity"
    },
    {
        "question": "If you want to _____ your weight, think about exercising more instead of eating less.",
        "answer": "reduce"
    },
    {
        "question": "Creating a new way to fight certain types of cancer was the doctor’s best-known _____.",
        "answer": "achievement"
    },
    {
        "question": "What _____ of your salary do you save each month?",
        "answer": "percentage"
    },
    {
        "question": "We had a very _____ meeting yesterday, and we solved a lot of the problems with our project.",
        "answer": "productive"
    },
    {
        "question": "After studying a little bit of English each day, I really noticed that my speaking ability started to _____.",
        "answer": "improve"
    },
    {
        "question": "I really studied hard this semester, and it resulted in a _____ improvement in my final grade for the class.",
        "answer": "notable"
    },
    {
        "question": "Susan made the largest _____ to the group project by working so hard to make sure that everything was correct in the report.",
        "answer": "contribution"
    },
    {
        "question": "When there are too many people who can't get jobs, the whole _____ suffers.",
        "answer": "economy"
    },
    {
        "question": "I can’t wait to _____ the Northern Lights in Iceland. If you come with me, it would be perfect!",
        "answer": "experience"
    },
    {
        "question": "The best thing that a teacher can do is to make sure that his or her students leave school with _____ knowledge in their chosen fields.",
        "answer": "informed"
    },
    {
        "question": "If you want to improve your test scores, you should try to _____ your diet. Good nutrition really helps you remember better.",
        "answer": "improve"
    },
    {
        "question": "The _____ in the boy’s dormitory is not very good. It is always a little dirty, and it smells quite bad.",
        "answer": "sanitation"
    },
    {
        "question": "One of the most _____ industries of Taiwan is its computer chip manufacturing.",
        "answer": "notable"
    },
    {
        "question": "When you _____ something, you try to explain what it means.",
        "answer": "define"
    },
    {
        "question": "The most recent _____ has caused a lot of problems for the world’s economies.",
        "answer": "pandemic"
    },
    {
        "question": "Many people consider kindness to one another to be the highest _____ of humanity.",
        "answer": "ideal"
    },
    {
        "question": "A lot of people like to _____ in order to help their communities.",
        "answer": "volunteer"
    },
    {
        "question": "Over the last ten years, the _____ of students who leave Taiwan to study for Master’s degrees has been increasing.",
        "answer": "percentage"
    },
    {
        "question": "My classmates and I are going to Thailand to _____ to teach Chinese this winter.",
        "answer": "volunteer"
    }
]